Right now, open your lips.
You have aspirations to get to a certain position but family limitations are there.
Right now, open your lips and begin to break every cycle of limitation.
Open your lips right now, begin to break every family limitation.
Break it right now and move.
I join you to break it, in the name of Jesus.
I join you to break them, in the name of Jesus.
Two believers are better than one.
I join you to break that family limitation, in the name of Jesus.
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Every family limitation - be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Every family limitation, in Jesus' name - be broken!
Be broken, in the name of Jesus!
Aspiration to get to a certain area of life,
to get to a certain position,
to get certain things done
to get certain things achieved
but family limitation is there.
I got out of it, you must get out of it.
You must get out of it!
Say, I must get out of it!
Because of Christ, I must get out of it!
Open your lips and begin to get out of it!
Begin to release your life!
SCOAN Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Not only position.
When you talk of health,
there are certain areas in your family - you learn about diabetes, hypertension, cancer.
You learn about this, about that in the same family.
Certain things cannot be done, cannot be achieved because of limitation in the family.
Family limitation, begin to break it right now!
Break out and open the cage!
Open the cage and come out!
SCOAN Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Yes!
You must come out of the cage.
Family limitation, community limitation, national limitation, come out!
You must come out of it.
Say, I must come out of it.
You must be released!
From sickness, you must be released!
Say, I must be released from infirmity!
I must be released from hardship!
I must be released from limitation!
I must be released from setback!
I must be released from poverty!
Be released!
Open your lips, release yourself!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Overflow Congregation
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Whatever challenges, situation you are facing - I release you, in the name of Jesus!
Challenges in your health,
challenges in your blood,
challenges in your fluid,
challenges in your bones,
challenges in your faculties,
be released, in the name of Jesus!
Because of Christ, whatever poison you might have eaten through dreams,
from the table of the enemy, begin to vomit it!
Come out!
Say, come out!
Out!
Overflow Congregation
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I declare you free!
I declare your blood free!
I declare your muscle free!
I declare your tendons free!
Every faculty of yours, be free!
Every faculty of yours, be healed!
In the name of Jesus!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Cover yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Purge yourself with the blood of Jesus.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
My business, be restored!
My finances, be released with the precious blood of Jesus!
Be released!
Be restored, in the name of Jesus!
Be restored, be released, in the name of Jesus!
My career, destiny - favour!
Mercy!
Favour!
In the name of Jesus!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
TT: Mel Flowers
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 29/06/2018